well got Thomas you are Chris you are
mortal men a steady blade balances the
soul come on
so cat cougar Iza
gingerly Shubin measure twice cut once
Waga Thomas Shiva King Cole moto-meter
my work here is done
madam Allah simple yes you are only
human how I was hoping for a challenge
Touche Johanna we hope my Halloween
costume
cyborg ninja oh gosh you're Kareena care
he does everything
count your blessings Merry Christmas all
bark no bite to know yourself is to be a
piece Kodama life and death balance on
the edge of my blade your eyes deceive
you the soul is an elegant weapon for
more civilized age I'm not impressed you
need a healing you seem nice I hate to
kill you
dude she Manju strikes